Curriculum Vitae

Wesley White

59 Scarlett Avenue, Wendover, Bucks, HP22 5BD https://hexthelight.co.uk

E:- wes.white@hexthelight.co.uk

M:- 07749 437466

About Myself

After nearly 10 years in the accounting profession I found a passion for technology born through learning about AWS and seeing just how much it can revolutionise business across all sectors. After studying it for over a year and using its various services I decided to make the change into tech. I am a keen problem solver and love getting stuck in to find the best solution for the client.

Professional Certifications

e-Careers	Comptia Cloud+	Mar 2021
e-Careers	AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner	May 2021
e-Careers	AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate	Oct 2021
e-Careers	AgilePM Foundation	Aug 2021
Microsoft	Azure Fundamentals AZ-900	Dec 2021
Hashicorp	Terraform Associate	Dec 2021
BCS	Foundation in Digital Solutions Development	May 2022
BPP	AAT Level 4	2019
UX Design Institute	Certified UX Designer	2020

Education

Chesham Grammar School	3 A Levels incl. Maths at grade B	2012
Amersham School	7 GCSE's A*-C	2010

Technical Skills

- Competent with Linux systems across Fedora, Arch and Debian based systems, confident in using the command line and have experience creating and running bash scripts
- Competent with HTML, CSS and JS and can build static webpages and host them on EC2, ECS, S3 and Cloudfront
- Experienced with both the AWS Console and the CLI to create cloud infrastructure, interact with services such as S3 and Route 53 and maintain my web servers with high availability using AWS S3 and Cloudfront
- Competent with Windows and can perform basic maintenance with command prompt and powershell, familiar and experienced with Remote Desktop Connection
- Familiar with Git and have experience building a full CI/CD pipeline with AWS CodePipeline
- Competent in Python (including usage of the AWS SDK's with AWS Lambda) and currently studying
- Experience using both Cloudformation and Terraform to create cloud infrastructure and build a web server
- Experience working with Docker containers and basic use of Docker compose files

Personal Skills

- Able to work both individually or as part of a team to deliver the client requirements effectively
- Committed to providing the best solutions for the client
- Keen problem solver with an eye for detail
- Friendly and highly adaptable to the situation in hand
- I am a guick learner and always willing to try different approaches

Achievements

- Successfully migrated the accounting function for an international call centre company to the cloud accounting package Xero across 7 countries and ran training for their UK and Phillipines operations
- Black Belt in Northern Shaolin Chin Wu Kung Fu
- 3rd Place in BCCMA National Championship for Kung Fu
- BCCMA National Championship Good Sportsman Award
- Participated in the Queen's Golden Jubilee Procession

<u>Personal Projects</u>

Current Projects

- Hosting FOSS software such as Diagrams.net using ECS Fargate to create an all-in-one workflow management suite for myself self-hosted with AWS to enable better control of my data
- Exploring hybrid storage using AWS Storage Gateway with an on-premises server to operate as an off site backup for crucial data as well as for archiving purposes
- Creating a DevOps playground to allow me to test out technologies like Hashicorp Vault, Ansible and Puppet using a secure AWS environment whilst following best practices
- Created a Lambda function using Python to demonstrate how to automate the folder structure of objects uploaded to an S3 bucket to allow for easier recall and further automation based on certain metrics (i.e. file type)

E-Careers and Optima

- Mentor in the Optima and e-Careers AWS Academy
- Help students with AWS exam preparation for both CCP and Solutions Architect exams
- Training students on labs including creating a web server using EC2 and increasing availability by building in a load balancer and auto scaling group

Career History

Technical Architect 6point6 Limited Mar 2022 - Present

- Working in the public sector to help design and implement transformative services to increase
 efficiency and help the client adapt quickly to fast-moving requirements and aid in their transition
 away from their legacy platforms
- Working with multiple stakeholders across multiple fields including SecOps, DevOps, Developers and leadership and management teams
- Working internally to design, build and deploy a technical assessment platform which is hosted on AWS using Docker and RDS.
- Co-chair the green team to help the company achieve their goal of joining The Climate Pledge and being Net Zero carbon by 2040

Cloud Accounting Specialist Hillier Hopkins LLP Feb 2017 – Feb 2022

- Oversaw the Sublime bookkeeping entity, building out the systems and processes to be able to support a growing service list and client requirements
- Oversaw all app advisory services within the firm, including moving clients from legacy desktop
 applications to cloud accounting software such as Xero. This included scoping and designing
 solutions for the client from initial conversations, completing the migration and conducting all
 post-live support including training and follow up advisory as needs changed
- Advised and trained both clients and staff members on new ways of working using automation at the core of the finance function to eliminate manual entry and therefore allow greater accuracy and analytics
- Developed and implemented the firm's response to the CBILS loan scheme as a result of the COVID-19 pandemic to allow quick access to cash flow finance for our clients

Trainee Accountant SJD Accountancy Aug 2014 – Feb 2017

• Designed and implemented an automatic IR35 calculation spreadsheet for those caught by IR35 regulation for easier processing and to remove manual entry

Junior Accountant Thomas Cox & Co Jan 2013 – Jul 2014

Interests and Hobbies

- In my spare time I am an avid follower of motorsport, including Formula 1, Formula E and Indycar amongst others
- I enjoy cooking in the evenings and finding new recipes to try out
- I am always looking out for new FOSS software to experiment with and improve my usage of Linux
- I am always keen to try and build something new and make my own, from guitars to mechanical keyboards to websites

References available on request